top of page

* More

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

File Manager Plus

Last updated November 16th, 2023

​

This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. This Privacy Policy governs your use of the software application File Manager Plus (“Application”) for mobile devices that was created by AlphaInventor, Inc.. The Application is the file explorer that helps you manage your files and folders in your device, NAS(Network-attached storage) and cloud storages like Dropbox and Google Drive.

What information does the Application obtain?

User Provided Information 

When using the application, as appropriate, you may be asked to provide personal information. Personal information includes data such as (a) your name, email address, age, gender; (b) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us; (c) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (d) credit card information for purchase and use of the Application, and; (e) information you enter into our system when using the Application, such as contact information.

With your permission, the Application access information from your device, such as photo library, installed application list, and external SD card in order to function properly. If you choose to give us access, you may also link your use of the services with your cloud storage accounts.

​

Files on shared device storage 

Files on shared device storage are used only to provide the services you have requested, such as file management, etc.

​

Cloud service user data

User data collected from cloud services (Google Drive, Dropbox, OneDrive, etc.) are used only to provide the services you have requested, such as file management, etc.

​

Automatically Collected Information 

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application. 

​

Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?

This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device. 

​

How is your information used and why?

The information collected from you is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve the service, (ii) to administer your use of the service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide or offer application updates and announcements.

Where we need to process your personal information either to comply with law, or to perform the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that information when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with the functionalities of the Services). In this case, we may have to stop you using our Services.

Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

1. as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
    
2. when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
    
3. with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.
    
4. if AlphaInventor,Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.
    
5. to analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. (You can view analytics company whom we work with in Appendix 1.)
    
6. to advertisers and third party advertising networks in the section below.

Automatic Data Collection and Advertising

We work with advertisers and third party advertising networks, who need to know how you interact with advertising provided in the Application which helps us keep the cost of the Application low. Advertisers and advertising networks use some of the information collected by the Application, including, but not limited to, the unique identification ID of your mobile device and your mobile telephone number. To protect the anonymity of this information, we use an encryption technology to help ensure that these third parties can’t identify you personally. These third parties may also obtain anonymous information about other applications you’ve downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit, your non-precise location information (e.g., your zip code), and other non- precise location information in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Application and elsewhere. We may also share encrypted versions of information you have provided in order to enable our partners to append other available information about you for analysis or advertising related use. 

What are my choices with my personal information?

If you’d like us to access to, correct, update, or delete User Provided Information that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at support @ alphainventor.com. We will respond in a reasonable time. We may ask you for proof of account ownership and/or identity before fulfilling your request. This is a security measure to ensure that your information is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Information may be required in order for the Application to function properly.

For Residents in the EU

The General Data Protection Regulation (also known as GDPR) provides you with additional rights regarding your personal information. If you are within the EU, you have the right to:

Request access to your personal information. This enables you to receive a copy of the information we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.

Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it.

Object to processing of your personal information. This right exists where we are relying on a legitimate interest as the legal basis for our processing and there is something about your particular situation, which makes you want to object to processing of your information on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your information for direct marketing purposes.

Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your information, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.

Request the transfer of your personal information. We will provide to you your Information in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

Withdraw consent. This right only exists where we are relying on consent to process your information ("Consent Withdrawal"). If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you with access to the certain specific functionalities of our Service. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

If you want to exercise any of the rights described above or submit a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an email to support @ alphainventor.com with “GDPR Request” in the subject line. In the email please describe, with specificity, the GDPR right you are requesting assistance with. If you feel that your complaint has not been adequately resolved, please note that the GDPR gives you the right to contact your local data protection supervisory authority.

For Residents of California

The California Consumer Privacy Act (also known as CCPA) provides you with additional rights regarding your personal information. If you are a California resident, these terms and conditions apply to you.

In the preceding 12 months, we may have collected from you or from your use of the services, categories of personal information as defined under the CCPA, which includes the following:

1. Identifiers such as your name, email address, IP address, unique device identifiers, advertising identifiers, online identifier, and other similar identifier;
    
2. Protected Classifications, such as your gender and age
    
3. Commercial information such as your payment method and related information if you purchase a subscription;
    
4. Internet or other electronic network activity information, including the name of your mobile operator, your brows type, language and time zone.
    
5. Interaction with our software or apps such as usage data, type and version of operating system, hardware version, device settings, software types, battery and signal strength, screen resolution, device manufacturer and model, language, and Internet browser type and version;

In the preceding 12 months, we may have used and disclosed personal information for the business and commercial purposes.

If you are a California resident, you have the right to:

Access specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you in the last 12 months.

Request to know the categories of personal information we have collected about you and the purposes for doing so; the categories of sources of that data; the categories of third parties with whom we shared it for a business purpose and our purposes for doing so.

Request deletion of your personal information.

Opt out of sales of personal information. To opt out of receiving interest-based advertising, you can exercise your choice by using your settings.

Receive equal service and not be discriminated against even if you exercise any of your CCPA rights.

​

Data Retention Policy

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. 

​

Children

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support @ alphainventor.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

​

Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. 

​

Your Consent

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at support @ alphainventor.com.

​

File Manager Plus - Privacy Policy: Text

Appendix 1. Third party service provider
----------------------------------------

File Manager Plus - Privacy Policy: HTML Embed

©2023 by AlphaInventor, Inc.

bottom of page
